==============================================================================================================

**Information Collected and Stored Automatically**  
When you visit the BBN web sites, if you do nothing during your visit but browse through the web site, read pages, or download information, we will gather and store certain information about your visit automatically. This information does not identify you personally. We automatically collect and store only the following aggregated general information about your visit:

* the pages you visit,
* the date and time you access our site,
* the name of the domain from which you access the Internet (for example, aol.com, if you are coming from an America Online account, or bju.edu if you are connecting from Bob Jones University’s domain),
* the Internet address of the website from which you linked directly to our site, and
* your operating system and browser.

We use this information:

* to measure the number of visitors to the various sections of our site,
* to help us make our site more useful
* to develop and code content pages so that most people will be able to view the pages correctly.

**If You Send Us Personal Information**  
If you choose to provide us with personal information, as in an e-mail message or by filling out a form, we store the question and e-mail address information just long enough to answer the question that was sent in, and send the answer back to the e-mail or other address or phone number provided. If you send us a comment, we relay the comment to the most appropriate staff member. If enough questions or comments come in that are the same, the question may be added to one of our help or FAQ pages, or the suggestions may be used to guide the design of our Web site. Unless otherwise required by statute, we do not identify publicly who sends questions or comments into our web site.

**Children’s Privacy**  
Children under 13 years of age are not encouraged or invited to contact BBN via our webs sites. When a child under age 13 contacts BBN via an unsolicited e-mail or unsolicited chat, we do not store their personal information or carry on communication beyond what is necessary to provide the ministry related information requested. The nature of our reply is limited to providing ministry related information one-time to a one-time request. Unless otherwise required by statute, we never disclose any personal information to 3rd parties.

We never condition a child’s participation in an activity on the child’s disclosing more personal information than is reasonably necessary to participate in that activity. All personally identifiable information we do collect for one-time responses can only be accessed by authorized BBN staff and only those people who require access may see this information. We preserve the confidentiality, security, and integrity of that information.

**BBN News updates by e-mail**  
If you subscribe to BBN Global eNews in any language, BBN considers your e-mail address confidential and it will not be released.

**BBN Chat**  
BBN chats are considered “instant messaging” rather than a “chat room”. Each instant message session takes place with one BBN staff member or volunteer that has satisfied all the requirements of our training program. Identifiable personal information is never shared with 3rd parties, except when required by statute. To maintain accountability, all chats may be monitored live by BBN Chat administrative staff. Also, transcripts of all chats are maintained at least long enough for a BBN Chat Administrator to review each conversation. Administrators are the only ones able to review the transcripts. Their reviews are soley for the purpose of maintaining accountability and upholding the integrity of BBN. At no time do we knowingly chat with children under age 13. Warnings are posted along the path into the instant messaging environment to discourage the participation of children under 13. Further, our staff and volunteers are trained to politely end conversations with underage children that elect to ignore the warnings.

**Disclosure**  
BBN does not disclose, give, sell or transfer any personal information about our visitors, unless required for law enforcement or by statute. We will only use personally identifying information to respond to you or to help us perform our ministry duties. In those cases, various people may see the personal information you provide in order to look into the matter you inquired about.

Also, e-mail is not necessarily secure against interception. If you are worried because your communication is very sensitive, or includes personal information, you can send it by postal mail instead.

**Disclaimer of Endorsement & Links to Other Sites**  
Our web site has links to many other web sites. If you access another site through a link we provide, you are subject to the privacy policy of the new site.

Reference in this web site to any specific ministry, commercial products, process, service, manufacturer, or company does not constitute its endorsement or recommendation by BBN. BBN is not responsible for the contents of any ‘OFF-SITE’ web pages referenced from this server.

**Intrusion Detection**  
For site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all users, we employ software programs to monitor traffic and identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage. In the event of authorized law enforcement investigations, and pursuant to any required legal process, information from these sources may be used to help identify an individual.

This web site is operated by:

Bible Broadcasting Network  
11530 Carmel Commons Blvd.  
Charlotte, NC 28226  
(704) 523-5555

Visitors 13 and older may contact BBN for any reason using the contact form on our web site.

**Android Privacy Policy**

Device information

* We collect device-specific information (such as operating system version and mobile network information). Google may associate your device identifiers or phone number with your Google Account.
* We may collect and store information locally on your device using mechanisms such as browser web storage (including HTML 5) and application data caches.

How we use information we collect

* We use the information we collect from all of our services to provide, maintain, protect and improve them, to develop new ones. We also use this information to offer you our streaming with the best quality possible, depending your specific device.

### How to Get to Heaven

© Copyright - Bible Broadcasting Network
